

GUNA HARSHA

Manager-Operations

Energetic and experienced Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the retail & QSR industry. Skilled in Customer service & team Management, Operational activities, Communication, Microsoft Office, SLA metrics, and Variance Analysis. Strong professional with MBA focused in Inventory management, Procurement & supply chain.

①+91-8790920424 ①Hyderabad, India Gunaharsha04@outlook.com linkedin.com/in/guna-harsha-49a022212

WORK EXPERIENCE

Manager - Operations
Purple Style Labs Pvt.ltd

June 2022 – Present

Hyderabad, India

- Managing performance measures on operational/business goals and SLA metrics of online and store orders.
- Inventory control(Inbound & outbound logistics) & reconciliation of stocks.
- Managing stock discrepancies between stores & warehouses.
- Analyzing the missing stock and implementation of lean six sigma procedures to minimize stock shortages.
- Executing specific methods for training, Coaching & development of team.
- Resolving store operational related complaints on time for smooth functioning of operations.

Supply Chain Associate

Masala Tech F&B LLP

April 2022 – June 2022

Hyderabad, India

- End to end management of Kitchen inventory items (Perishable, non-perishable, cooking equipment and Packaging)
- Implemented cost-effective practices in procurement
- Liaison with vendors to ensure timely delivery of receivables
- ❖ Address Vendor related issues to achieve an amicable resolution
- Responsible for the Store inventory and maintaining par levels
- Create and implement SOPs to minimize wastage
- Owning level in invoice processing to ensure timely vendor payments.
- Develop reports to track inventory levels and wastage.

Operations shift manager

Starbucks India Pvt. Ltd

12/11/2018 – 17/03/2022(3years 4months)

Chennai, India

- Ensured high level of customer satisfaction through excellent customer service.
- Oversee the daily sales report every day and focused on ways to improve the business. Met sales goals by training, motivating, mentoring and providing feedback to the partners(employees).

- Completed stores operational requirements by scheduling; Engaging and training employees; Inventory and cashmanagement; Followed up on work results.
- Oversee food preparation, presentation, and storage to ensure compliance with food health and safety regulations.
- Scheduled the duties of the employees using work force management tool and analysed the staffing requirementsthrough Items Per Labour Hour (IPLH).
- Managed inventory tracking system every day to record stock levels and maintained PAR level according to therequirements.
- ❖ Focused on kaizen process and 5s Standards on the stocks every week and improved ways to reduce scrap and writeoff from 30% to 13%
- analyzed COGS and P&L account of the outlet and focused on reducing the controllable and consumables to increasethe profit of the outlet.

Team Leader

Nando's India Restaurants Pvt. Ltd 04/07/2017 – 05/10/2018(1year 3months)

Bangalore, India

- ❖ Trained restaurant staff and Managed restaurant staff's work schedule.
- Conducted regular inspections of the restaurant kitchen to determine whether proper standards of hygiene andsanitation were followed.
- Focused on customer reviews and to enquire about food quality and service. Resolving customer complaints at themoment.
- Monitored inventory and stock management and ensuring that all food supplies and other restaurant essentials areadequately stocked.
- Industrial training

Novotel Visakhapatnam Varun Beach 27th July 2015 – 23rd Oct 2017

Vizag, AP, India

❖ Worked in four core departments (food production, F&B service, Housekeeping & front office) in the hotel and gained practical knowledge and skills.

CERTIFICATION

Certified Coffee Master

Starbucks India Pvt.ltd

June 2021

Certified Lean Six Sigma Green Belt

International Institute of management and quality

Nov 2021

EDUCATION

MBA in Logistics and Supply chain Management

Vels University 2020-2022

Chennai, India

B.Sc. Hospitality and Hotel Administration

Institute of Hotel Management 2014-2017

Chennai, India

PROJECT

MINI PROJECT:

"Real time project on reducing the delivery time using Minitab Firm: Sangeetha Restaurant

DESCRIPTION:

To reduce the home delivery time from 40mins to 25mins during weekends by applying DMAIC.

DOMAIN		Food industry (Reducing the delivery time)
SIX S I G MA	DEFINE	Project selection, Smart goal fixation, business case, CTC, CTQ, Project charter, Ganttchart, CPM, SIPOC
	MEASURE	Control charts, Pareto analysis, Mean, median, mode, S.D, Variance, Normality test, Probability plots, Histogram
	ANALYZE	Pareto, hypothesis testing, correlation, regression, cause and effect analysis
	IMPROVE	Error proofing
	CONTROL	Trend charts

TECHNICAL SKILLS

1. MS office 2. ERP (sap)

LANGUAGES

1. English 2. Telugu 3. Hindi 4. Tamil

INTERESTS



DECLARATION

I hereby declare that all the details mentioned above information is correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Date:

Place: Hyderabad (GUNA HARSHA)

